we are going to take this tool and keep expanding it. eventually I will rename the entire directory but for now this is called the
   EliteSoftware_Extension_Framework. I would like you to add another property sheet this one does not need a stand alone window but
   it does need to pass the current file into another program with a button to open inside main app. I want it to be a windows media
   player viewer that would show up when the user right clicks and clicks properties on any file type that is supported in windows
   media player. it would work just like the preview pane implementation of the media player.